Michael Fedorovsky

System Administrator | IT Programmer | Network Administrator | DevOps | Production Engineer

Contact Information

Email: michaelovsky5@gmail.com

Phone: 054-7632418

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/michael-fedorovsky-b26099278/

About Me

My name is Michael, I am 28 years old and live in central Israel. I am a technology and innovation enthusiast with a passion for solving technical problems and focusing on challenging IT environments. I specialize in navigating complex technical scenarios and am committed to excellence in every project or task. I have self-learning abilities and enjoy learning independently. I am motivated and eager to develop in the field and give as much of myself as possible.

Work Experience

Customer Service • Pemi Premium • 2020 - 2022

Hybrid work managing and retaining company customers, providing solutions and problem-solving. Meeting tasks and communicating with suppliers, customers, and company employees.

Security • A. Security • 2022 - 2024

Maintaining the physical security of the building residents and the entire living environment. Monitoring and maintaining security systems. Conducting patrols.

Education

Engineering Preparatory Program • 2022-2021 • Ariel University

Studying Mathematics, Physics, and English. Completing assignments and exams. I successfully completed the program.

Knowledge and Skills

Programming and Scripting Languages: Bash, Python, PowerShell, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Network Technologies: Experience with TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP, VPN, managing and maintaining firewalls (pfSense, Fortigate, Cisco ASA, etc.), and switching and routing protocols.

Virtualization: VMware, VirtualBox, Proxmox, Qemu, ESXi, Hyper-V.

Process Control and Automation: Experience with Ansible and Terraform.

Cloud Technologies: Knowledge in managing and securing cloud systems (AWS, GCP, Azure)

Operating Systems: Linux and Windows administration and server systems, regular maintenance of systems and servers

Additional Technologies: Regular use of Docker, Docker Swarm, and Kubernetes. Also proficient in remote controlling servers.

Volunteering

2016 - 2018 Animal Welfare Tel Aviv Two years of volunteering at an animal shelter, caring for and assisting in the adoption of animals, mainly dogs, while developing compassion and empathy towards animals.

Military Service

2014-2016 Air Force Service in a control and monitoring unit, managing the main control panel, and monitoring the activities of the corps.